A project of mine.
Keep in mind, this is beta, release will be a decent mod.
As of now mostly everything is crappy.

V0.3

Added Xzyer and the first ever sword in a long list.

Xzyer: "Flies" around the player and heals mana and health, counts as a pickaxe and a axe.

Golden Test Sword (GTS): The first sword of about 80 to be added,
it is just OP as of now, however,
the swords will create a crafting line for the omniverse and multiverse sets.

Planned items.

Respriting True's wings (They are disgusting)

Respriting ZX Blade

Fixing Omniverse sprites and finishing the set.

Adding the Multiverse set

Adding the sword crafting line.